savorymobile.com 2014-09-11

# Savory Mobile - Powerful Technology for Restaurants

Savory Mobile, as the provider of this Mobile Application, is committed to protecting the privacy of your personally identifiable information, herein after referred to as “PII”. Personally identifiable information is information that identifies you as an individual. The following privacy policy sets forth the manner in which we collect, use, share, and protect the personally identifiable information you provide when using the application. This policy does not address the collection, use or disclosure of information by any of our affiliates or by third parties. 

This privacy policy is subject to change at any time and notice of any changes made will become effective as of the posting date. The posting will be listed at the top of the privacy policy page as the effective date. 

* **What is considered Personally Identifiable Information, “PII”?**

Savory Mobile, as the provider of the mobile application that is the subject of this privacy policy, supports mobile ordering platforms for restaurants that subscribe to our service. In order for you to take advantage of the ordering systems provided, you are required to furnish personally identifiable information which Savory Mobile receives and collects. The personal information collected includes but is not limited to, first name, last name, street address, city, zip code, phone number, e-mail address, credit card information, Twitter and or Facebook user names, and browser information. 

* **Why your “PII” is collected?**

Collection of your “PII” enables you to use the “APP” powered by Savory Mobile to create an account, place an order through our restaurant subscriber’s mobile ordering platform, authorize and process your credit or debit card purchase, send you important information regarding changes to this Privacy Policy or Terms of Use, and for our internal business processes such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our website, and improving our services. 

* **How is your PII Collected?**

You may use this subscribing resturaunt’s APP in one of two ways. You may either use the APP as a guest on a per order basis, or may you choose to save your information by creating an account with Savory Mobile. In order to create an account you must disclose personally identifiable information during the registration process. The information required to create an account includes but is not limited to, first name, last name, street address, city, zip code, phone number, e-mail address, credit card information, Twitter and or Facebook user names, and browser information. 

In addition to personal information you provide, Savory Mobile uses "cookies" to store the personal information your provde through account registration. See the following link for a more information on “cookies”. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie. 

We may also use and read cookies for other purposes, including to collect information on how our site is used, to improve performance for our users, and to provide you with information of potential interest to you. 

Most web browsers are set up to accept cookies. You can, however, set your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being created. Note, however, that some portions of our site may not work properly if you refuse cookies. In addition, cookies can be easily and safely deleted from your system. 

* **How is your PII protected?**

We use industry standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving private consumer data on our site. This information can only be translated once it's received by our secure servers. These secure servers help to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you through our Web site. 

The personally identifiable information you provide when you create an account with Savory Mobile is protected by a password, selected by you, for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately, and limiting access to your computer, browser, or mobile phone by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

Savory Mobile endeavors to safeguard user information to ensure that user account information is kept private. However, Savory Mobile cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

* **Use of PII and Information Sharing**

Savory Mobile will not disclose your personal information to any person or entity except (i) in order to process your food order, Savory Mobile must share the following information every time you place an order with a restaurant: your name, delivery address, food order, telephone number and e-mail address. This information will be provided to the restaurant from who you have ordered as well as any delivery service providers if necessary. Additionally, Savory Mobile will share certain personal financial information required in order to complete the transaction with the credit card processing company. 

Restaurants may use your personal information to contact you concerning products, services and promotions which may be of interest to you. Upon receiving your permission, we may share your personal information with such third parties to advise you of products, services and promotions. The use of your personal information provided to such third parties is governed by their privacy policies. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by SAVORY MOBILE. Therefore, we disclaim any liability for any third party's use of your personal Information in a manner in conflict with this or their own privacy policy. 

We may also disclose your personal information to comply with legal obligations, law enforcement inquiries or where reasonably necessary to protect life, health or property. 

In the event that Savory Mobile is sold, merged into or otherwise transferred to or acquired by another entity, your information that we have collected may be transferred to and used by that other entity. 

* **Updating or Deleting your PII.**

Savory Mobile allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and updating that information and ensuring that it is accurate and complete. You can access this information on the Savory Mobile website by visiting the MY ACCOUNT page. This list is subject to change as our Services change. 

  * Password
  * Phone number
  * Email address
  * Other User profile information (“my favorites”)

Should you ever decide to delete your Savory Mobile account, you may do so by clicking on the "delete account" link on the MY ACCOUNT page. 

Deleted information may remain in out database for purposes of historical data preservation. 

* **Links to Third Party Websites.**

You may be offered services, products and promotions provided by third parties and not by Savory Mobile. If you decide to use these Third Party Services you will be responsible for reviewing and understanding the terms and conditions associated with these services. You agree that Savory Mobile is not responsible for the performance of these services. The Savory Mobile website may contain links to third party websites as a convenience to you. The inclusion of any website link does imply an approval, endorsement, or recommendation by Savory Mobile. You agree that you access any such website at your own risk, and that the site is not governed by the terms and conditions contained in this privacy policy. Savory Mobile expressly disclaims any liability for these websites. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. 

* **Children 13 or under.**

The application provided by Savory Mobile is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. We request that such individuals do not provide PII through the site. 

* **Email Opt Out Provisions**

Savory Mobile, as the provider of the application for the subscriber restaurant, will not sell or share your e-mail address with anyone other than the restaurant for which you are accessing this application or the credit card processing company that processes your payment. We may send you promotional e-mails from time to time unless you elect to opt out of the promotions. TO OPT OUT PLEASE ACCESS THE “MY ACCOUNT” PAGE AND SELECT THE “E-MAIL OPT OUT” OPTION. 

* **Your California Privacy Rights**

California law requires that you be allowed to opt of our sharing of your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and wish to opt out please select the CA RESIDENT OPT OUT PROVISION on the “MY ACCOUNT” page. 

* **Questions or Concerns.**

Any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy should be directed in writing to Savory Mobile at support@savorymobile.com.
